We are here with our group chat topic about student protests and our headliner of the week
Kimberly Renee you hear her every week just schooling us on why you bring it up all ish
like historically would you agree Kimberly that at the end of any final stage of an empire or
colonial colonialist empire that they just start grasping at straws and being wild extra
yes but I would also say that the children rising up is always towards the end as well
yeah like when I think about uh St. Augustine what happened in St. Augustine Florida like they
started shipping in children from all over the country teenagers into St. Augustine and that was
the moment when they saw you probably remember these photos of like the policemen um and the dogs
sicking the children and they were spraying them with like water hoses that moment led to um the
Civil Rights Act I think of 1964 like that was that moment they were in the public eye because it's
like how dare you hurt the children and that was the pressure that was needed in order to
you know for us to see actual change in legislation so I feel like we've seen that multiple times
well I think we're also in times where we're going to see things that we've seen
but like in a whole new world it's a wild time
we are we are we are